{
  "duration": "10",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "A collection of related data.",
      "options": [
        "Information",
        "Valuable information",
        "Database",
        "Metadata"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "A collection of related data.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correctOption": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "DBMS manages the interaction between __________ and database.",
      "options": ["Users", "Clients", "End Users", "Stake Holders"],
      "correctOption": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "Which of the following is not involved in DBMS?",
      "options": ["End Users", "Data", "Application Request", "HTML"],
      "correctOption": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Database is generally __________",
      "options": [
        "System-centered",
        "User-centered",
        "Company-centered",
        "Data-centered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "A characteristic of an entity.",
      "options": ["Relation", "Attribute", "Parameter", "Constrain"],
      "correctOption": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "The restrictions placed on the data.",
      "options": ["Relation", "Attribute", "Parameter", "Constraint"],
      "correctOption": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "IMS stands for?",
      "options": [
        "Information Mastering System",
        "Instruction Management System",
        "Instruction Manipulating System",
        "Information Management System"
      ],
      "correctOption": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "A model developed by Hammer and Mc Leod in 1981.",
      "options": ["SDM", "OODBM", "DDM", "RDM"],
      "correctOption": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "Object=_________+relationships.",
      "options": ["data", "attributes", "entity", "constraints"],
      "correctOption": 3
    }
  ]
}
